Privacy Policy
==============

Thank you for visiting [literacentre.com](https://literacentre.com/). We respect your individual privacy and value your confidence in us. We hold the privacy of your personal information in the highest regard, thus safeguarding it is a matter of the utmost importance. As a part of this commitment to protect our customers’ privacy, we have determined and implemented 10 privacy parameters to govern our actions.

The Privacy Parameters are as follows:
--------------------------------------

* Parameter 1 - Accountability: We hold the responsibility of maintaining and protecting personal information under our control. We have designated one person accountable for Litera Centre to ensure everything falls under privacy parameters.
* Parameter 2 - Identifying Purposes: We shall identify the purpose for which personal information is collected at or prior to the time of collection from the customer or the customer’s authorized person.
* Parameter 3 - Consent: The customer’s knowledge and consent are required for the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information except where the collection, use, and disclosure is needed and permitted by applicable law.
* Parameter 4 - Limiting Collection: The personal details collected will be limited and necessary to the purpose as identified by Literacentre.com. All the information will be collected by fair and lawful means.
* Parameter 5 - Limiting Use, Disclosure, and Retention: The customer’s personal information will only be used or disclosed for the purpose it is collected unless consented by the customer or permitted and applicable by the law. Personal information will only be retained for the period of time it is required to fulfil professional or legal liabilities.
* Parameter 6 - Accuracy: Literacentre.com must maintain personal information in an accurate, complete and up-to-date form as it is necessary to fulfil the purpose for which it is collected and to be used.
* Parameter 7 - Safeguarding Personal Information: Personal information at Literacentre.com is protected by security technologies and safeguards against unauthorized access and misuse that are appropriate to the sensitivity of the collected information.
* Parameter 8 - Openness and Transparency: Literacentre.com will provide customers with information regarding privacy policy and data management that involves their personal information.
* Parameter 9 - Customer Access: Upon request and with reasonable justification customer should be informed of the existence, use, and disclosure of their personal information and shall be given access to it. Customers should be able to verify the accuracy and completeness of their personal information and may request that it be amended if required.
* Parameter 10 - Handling Customer Complaints and Suggestions: Customers may direct their questions or enquires with respect to the Privacy parameters or about our practices by contacting the designated person accountable for privacy at Literacentre.com or email us at [info@literacentre.com](mailto:info@literacentre.com?subject=Literacentre%20Enquiry)

How to contact us?
------------------

Customers may direct any questions or inquire with respect to our practices or your personal information by contacting our Privacy Officer, as follows: [info@literacentre.com](mailto:info@literacentre.com?subject=Literacentre%20Enquiry)

#### WAIT BUT WHY ?

When your demo class is free !!!
--------------------------------

Book Demo Form (#6)

First Name

Last Name

Email

Phone/Mobile

Curriculum

\- Select Your Curriculum-International BaccalaureateIGCSEAS/A LevelSAT Exam PreparationACTAP (Advanced Placement)

Grade

\- Select Your Grade-MYP 1MYP 2MYP 3MYP 4MYP 5DP 1DP 2

Grade

\- Select Your Grade-IG 6IG 7IG 8IG 9IG 10

Grade

\- Select Your Grade-AS LevelA Level

Subject

\- Select Your Subject-Language and LiteratureFrenchSpanishHindiIndividuals and SocietiesSciencesMathematics

Subject

\- Select Your Subject-ScienceMathematicsEnglish

Subject

\- Select Your Subject-English Language and LiteratureHindiFrenchSpanishGermanEconomicsGeographyGlobal PerspectivesHistoryBiologyChemistryPhysicsMathematics - Core & ExtendedMathematics

Subject

\- Select Your Subject-English LanguageEnglish LiteratureGeographyEconomicsHistoryFrenchSpanishHindiMathematicsPhysicsChemistryBiology

Subject

\- Select Your Subject-Language and Literature SLLanguage and Literature HLFrench SLFrench HLSpanish SLSpanish HLHindi SLHindi HLBusiness Management SLBusiness Management HLEconomics SLEconomics HLGeography SLGeography HLHistory SLHistory HLPhysics SLPhysics HLChemistry SLChemistry HLBiology SLBiology HLMathematics Analysis and Approaches SLMathematics Analysis and Approaches HLMathematics Applications and Interpretation SLMathematics Applications and Interpretation HL

Subject

\- Select Your Subject-Language and LiteratureFrenchSpanishHindiIndividuals and SocietiesPhysicsChemistryBiologyMathematics

Submit

We bring you a world-class international (both Indian and expat) team of highly experienced and qualified faculty.

### Education

### Quick Links

### Have Questions ?

Copyright 2024. All rights reserved with [Litera Centre](https://cvngp04.na1.hs-sales-engage.com/Ctc/5B+23284/cvngp04/Jks2-6qcW69sMD-6lZ3pXVzxkp11m6Yw_N6BplH7J3Dk-W7px5zJ9dDWLGN54sv0Jwj7sSW1S72Gw4vNFQrN6x1L1tr49FNW5lHh572-QCPpW80xrfv1hqjVHW27y0_p3d1bBgW3PRCpR5hHHhYW18_tTp6nmRKlW8109fz6TYJy1W5TXccx17Zq1ZW71NW964PbVKHW3J4PYv6v76swW6NLGmd8trcbkW2sLxQb6--jnhW3lff9Z86fV8nW6c7JSd4c-KsbW2-1Rt710fQfNf1r383K04), part of Socratic Education powered by Socratic Education Pvt. Ltd.

[Enroll  
Now](https://www.literacentre.com/enrollment-form/)

New Launch

More Affordable with Micro Group Classes
----------------------------------------

Get the same quality as 1-on-1 Classes in a more affordable way. knowledgeable and committed teachers offer a plethora of expertise. 

* **Micro Group Classes**(3-4 Students in a Class)
* Live Classes
* Inernational Baccalaureate & Cambridge Certified Tutors

[Enroll Free Demo Session

Book Now](https://www.literacentre.com/book-demo-class/)

### Get Amazon Voucher $25

Refer a friend and earn Amazon Voucher Worth $25(or equivalent to your local currency)

Refer a Friend

Full Name

Your Phone/Mobile

Referred Student First Name

Referred Student Last Name

Contact Number of Referred Student

Curriculum of Referred student

\- Select Curriculum of Referred student-IBIGCSE/GCSEAS/A Level

Any additional comments or information you would like to provide?

Email id of Referred Student

Subject of Referred student

Your Full Address to get a reward of Amazon Voucher

Avail Your Offer Now!

Book Your 

 IB 

 IGCSE 

 AS/A Level 

 SAT Exam Preparation 

Demo Class

Personalized Learning
---------------------

* 1:1 Live Classes
* Micro Group Class
* Expert guidance
* Tailored sessions

Online Class
------------

Book Demo Blog Archive Pages (#19)

First Name

Last Name

Email

Phone/Mobile

Curriculum

\- Select Your Curriculum/Course -International BaccalaureateIGCSEAS/A LevelSATACTAP

Grade

\- Select Your Grade -MYP 1MYP 2MYP 3MYP 4MYP 5DP 1DP 2

Grade

\- Select Your Grade -IG 6IG 7IG 8IG 9IG 10

Grade

\- Select Your Grade -AS LevelA Level

Subject

\- Select Your Subject -ScienceMathematicsEnglish

Subject

\- Select Your Subject -Language and LiteratureFrenchSpanishHindiIndividuals and SocietiesSciencesMathematics

Subject

\- Select Your Subject -English LanguageEnglish LiteratureGeographyEconomicsHistoryFrenchSpanishHindiMathematicsPhysicsChemistryBiology

Subject

\- Select Your Subject -English Language and LiteratureHindiFrenchSpanishGermanEconomicsGeographyGlobal PerspectivesHistoryBiologyChemistryPhysicsMathematics - Core & ExtendedMathematics

Subject

\- Select Your Subject -Language and Literature SLLanguage and Literature HLFrench SLFrench HLSpanish SLSpanish HLHindi SLHindi HLBusiness Management SLBusiness Management HLEconomics SLEconomics HLGeography SLGeography HLHistory SLHistory HLPhysics SLPhysics HLChemistry SLChemistry HLBiology SLBiology HLMathematics Analysis and Approaches SLMathematics Analysis and Approaches HLMathematics Applications and Interpretation SLMathematics Applications and Interpretation HL

Subject

\- Select Your Subject -Language and LiteratureFrenchSpanishHindiIndividuals and SocietiesPhysicsChemistryBiologyMathematics

Subject

\- Select Your Subject -QuantVerbalBoth(Quant+Verbal)

Subject

\- Select Your Subject -EnglishMathsScienceReading and Wrting Essay

Subject

\- Select Your Subject -HumanitiesScienceOther

Submit
